https://fair.org/about-fair/fair-privacy-policy/

FAIRNESS & ACCURACY IN REPORTING
Challenging media bias since 1986.
Internship Program
What’s FAIR?
What’s Wrong With the News?
EXTRA! NEWSLETTER
Subscribe to Extra!
STORE
FAIRFAIR is the national progressive media watchdog group, challenging corporate media bias, spin and misinformation. Challenging media bias since 1986
HOME
ABOUT
DONATE
COUNTERSPIN RADIO
EXTRA! NEWSLETTER
FAIR STUDIES
ISSUES / TOPICS
TAKE ACTION
“What’s FAIR?” by founder Jeff Cohen
What’s Wrong with the News? (FAIR overview)
What Journalists, Scholars and Activists Are Saying
Privacy & Online Giving
Email List Privacy Policy
When you subscribe to FAIR’s email list, you will receive a confirmation message from fair@fair.org. You must reply in order to activate your subscription. We will not add you to our list without your confirmation.
We will use your email address only to send you FAIR updates, alerts, event announcements and occasional fundraising. We will never sell or share your email address with anyone.
Unsubscribe at any time via the “unsubscribe” link that will appear at the end of every message you receive from FAIR.
FAIR’s Privacy Policy for subscribers and website visitors
FAIR is committed to your online privacy. FAIR servers may record the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software and operating system you use; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.
We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the site, to diagnose and correct system errors, and to improve the site and enhance your experience. We delete this information after one month. We do not connect this information to your name or identity. If you have subscribed to FAIR’s email list,  are using the same browser and computer, and haven’t cleared cookies from your browser, you won’t be interrupted nearly as often by our “sign up” popup boxes.
Transactions and Online Giving
All online financial transactions are handled through a service equipped with security measures to ensure the safest transactions possible. These measures will work to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of any data under FAIR’s control.
FAIR Store Purchases: When purchasing products or subscriptions to Extra! from the FAIR online store, any financial information you send to us will be saved with our banking records for verification of deposits and handling of refunds only.
Online giving: Details of these online donation transactions, including personal information or giving history, will not be shared with any individual or outside organization.
Extra! Privacy Policy
FAIR well understands how hard it is for public interest groups, with limited resources, to get their message out. Occasionally, we share our list of subscribers to Extra!—our print newsletter—with groups or publications we feel might be of interest to you. If you prefer that your name and address remain confidential, just let us know.  To stop getting direct mail altogether go to: https://www.dmachoice.org/register.php
For your convenience, here is the Do Not Call Registry link to stop receiving unwanted phone call (FAIR never uses phone services): https://www.donotcall.gov
We always offer you every possible opportunity to opt out of providing personal information. In cases where personal information is needed, e.g. web-based financial transactions, we will keep this information confidential.
About FAIR
About
Mission Statement
Staff & Associates
Contact FAIR
Internship Program
FAIR’s Financial Overview
Privacy & Online Giving
“What’s FAIR?” by founder Jeff Cohen
What’s Wrong with the News? (FAIR overview)
What Journalists, Scholars and Activists Are Saying
FIND US IN YOUR INBOX
Sign up to receive all of FAIR’s articles of media criticism and news analysis, sent directly to your email.
Or sign up to receive our Weekly Update on Friday, with links to all our latest work.
Email
How would you like to hear from us?
All Posts
Weekly Alerts
Subscribe
If you are human, leave this field blank.
What’s FAIR
FAIR is the national progressive media watchdog group, challenging corporate media bias, spin and misinformation. We work to invigorate the First Amendment by advocating for greater diversity in the press and by scrutinizing media practices that marginalize public interest, minority and dissenting viewpoints. We expose neglected news stories and defend working journalists when they are muzzled. As a progressive group, we believe that structural reform is ultimately needed to break up the dominant media conglomerates, establish independent public broadcasting and promote strong non-profit sources of information.
Contact
Fairness & Accuracy In Reporting124 W. 30th Street, Suite 201
New York, NY 10001
Tel: 212-633-6700
Email directory
Support
We rely on your support to keep running. Please consider donating.
DONATE
Sign up to receive all of FAIR’s articles of media criticism and news analysis, sent directly to your email.
Or sign up to receive our Weekly Update on Friday, with links to all our latest work.
Email
How would you like to hear from us?
All Posts
Weekly Alerts
Subscribe
If you are human, leave this field blank.
X
This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
